Fox Family and G. Fox & Co. Collection 0012.002.008b
Jewish Historical Society of Greater Hartford
- Series IV: Lewis Fox Collection
  - Correspondence, undated
  - Educational Background, undated
  - Friends and Associates, undated
  - Home/750 Prospect Av., Hartford/Auction of Contents, 1977
  - Letters to Newspapers, undated
  - Manuscripts, undated
  - Miscellaneous, undated
  - Obituaries and Condolences, I, undated
  - Obituaries and Condolences, II, undated
  - Passport, undated
  - Personal items/baby book, 1904
  - Professional Activities, undated
  - Publications/Annual Christmas and Hanukkah Message, undated
  - Speaking Engagements, undated
- Series V: Jacob Fox collection
  - Correspondence, undated
  - Home/750 Prospect Av., Hartford/Construction and Furnishing (1905-1906)
  - Home/750 Prospect Av., Hartford/Construction Expense Ledger (1905-1906)
  - Home/750 Prospect Av., Hartford/Inventory of Silver, 1926
  - Marriage, 1902
  - Passport, undated
  - Professional Activities, undated
  - Telephone book, ca. 1908
  - Travel, undated